[{"answer": "No.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Any regrets at your end that you did that?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "I said I've sat down this week with President Clinton, with President Ahmadinejad --", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "I'm sorry, say that again, Piers?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Well, as I said, the president always makes time for world leaders.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "Couldn't the president have found time to have met some of them or maybe even come on my show and met them?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Well, that's great advice for Mitt Romney.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "I'd rather be the underdog on that first debate, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Well, Mitt Romney has said a couple things since, piers.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "What does Mitt Romney do if Barack Obama does that?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "I'm going to.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Have you done that yet?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "I generally see the prime minister when he's in the United States.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "You will be seeing Netanyahu this week?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Well, I hope he will react positively.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "How will he react to this?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Well, first off, Piers, I would just contest one thing.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "What would happen if the Israelis say you know what, we're not sensing anyone's with us, we're going on our own here, we're gong to defend ourselves, we're going to launch a strike now against these nuclear sites in Iran -- if they do that, what does a Romney administration do?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Well, it was -- obviously it was a one-on-one conversation.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Do you know how the conversation went with Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "Were you?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Desperate to se you.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Because you have a spanking new stage, at vast expense which houses 250 people and you signed some absolutely gargantuan new deal worth tens and tens of millions of dollars.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "I don't -- I can't take it seriously enough to think that it's a threat but then people will say, oh, that's so silly for you to think, like --", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "What do you make of the election race?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Will you vote?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Yes, I did.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "You enjoyed that one, didn't you?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "I never had anyone bail on me once they were in the studio.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "People bailing on you?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Well, P. Diddy was 40 minutes late so I walked up to my office and I said, maybe it was 40, maybe it was like 30.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "Anybody good?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "That's what you were talking about.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Why would I ever be talking about you in my spare time, though?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Well, it was fine.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "How did that go?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "The one with the strange name who runs hotels, Andre", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Which one?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "I don't know about it if I have.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "You don't think so?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "I read the first seven chapters.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Have you read \"Fifty Shades of Grey\"?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Was there anything in there you hadn't already done yourself?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "I know you probably imagined differently and have several nights during the week when you go to bed.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "You surprise me.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "No manacles?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "It's unreadable.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "Did you read the entire trilogy?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "Just out of pure curiosity.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Why would you read that?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "I see you as a surrogate booker.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "You think I'm going to book Jen?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "At Jennifer's wedding?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "You know what, I was thinking about that, actually.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "You think you will ever get married?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "Great, thanks.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "I feel under pressure.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "I think running the United States of America is like running an enormous corporation.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "Let me ask you off the top, do you think, given the financial state of the country, that having somebody with Romney's business background and business brain is a good idea, or do you think that's not really necessary in a commander-in-chief, in a president?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "No, I think a lot of people are doing that.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "Do you think you could still do that today?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "I think he is much better off in a suit than -- than colored trousers or chino trousers.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "What's your view?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "I think they are trying to sort of like -- sort of like the normal guys next door.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "Alarming orange jacket there from Mr. Romney?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "My family has been affected by autism.", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "Why is this such a cause dear to you, Tommy?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "B-A-S --", "docId": "120928pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "How do you write your father's name?", "qSentId": 697}]